okay now there's two shots here one the
see that
there mhm that's the
unit that's thece that's the tube with a
what's the name on it right mhm that's
the whole unit now this one I that's a r
I drove down there on this no petrol at
all we used about a cup cup to a cup and
a half or a cup of cuple water to go
from here down to M George that's Kye
out to M George M right out of that unit
right this one here what's in that you
know that's the plate system is it no
that is just a um that is
just yeah that's
yeah that's that one now when we got
down there Ron didn't
accept um this he wanted to make another
one so he made this circle one right mhm
now that is very thin stainless and the
whole thing turned circular she expanded
when you she just out and I know didn't
blow up but that would then that was
doing then polluting that motor she had
no smoke no fumes no nothing on anything
else by petrol or by my unit put this
one on she done the same she polluted
she had pressure and that was anable we
lost all brakes we lost
all we had no slowing here okay and
that's
the
[Music]
right evacu
foring CER mesh it gets it out heat
better than solid CER has a negative mhm
solid stainless outside has a positive
two two is the best two tues neutral
tubes mhm
um outside the the mesh and what's the
gap on that yeah it's approximately 6
mil yeah about seven Gap gives you the
gas off really well Gap um and um you
have two two of those tubes neutral
tubes they don't touch anything either
end the gas will come off both of those
each one will drop your current in half
and you'll come down from say 75 amp
down to 5 in and get off twice the three
times the amount of gas is that this is
M pet had got um Square meing he said
would um he was hoping this would work
this does not work nowhere near as well
because the um the wire they sealed wire
mhm and they're just interlocked all
right right now the current seems to be
able to go through and past where
if you have welded mes if you have
um yes Sol welded mesh the current can't
circulate and go past you'll come down
to the square and break out in the four
ways and put your gas out if you have
solid
tubing first all you get a very very
small amount off the the face like these
wires of face M the gas starts coming
off the Bott really well because it is
being cut and it's rough no face it's no
shiny face
um little bit off the sides here if you
grind those sides or you cut those sides
in any way or rough It Up Gas rips out
there and you can see the difference
between us if you have the
mesh um like this heavier actually
better that other one this is the actual
size very large
this is um cut off the mesh what we had
in the units mhm got that it's an 8 8
mil square and the the the meterage or
the the next size to the next tole is 12
so it's it's n is 8 m Square 12 M
testing this will show that off these
bits
here you will get probably four times
the amount of gas is what you can get
off this stainless which is
sealed M and um that's the difference
just by those she interrupts the flow of
current it seems
B negative in the
[Music]
middle can you say that y okay just
going in actually should be above it you
want see the gas okay
sorry mate I just me to pull
away soon as we touch the negative in I
mean the positive in we will get gas of
our
negative okay now we're in solid
outside to a solid negative
center now you see positive does not put
off very
much negative puts off everything it
splits from negative out towards
positive does not meet with
positive see that so the outside should
be a um the outside should be a solid
[Music]
mhm
hydren
[Music]
oygen no no you're all the no you're
right but you get get it off both you
get both off both positive is not an
oxygen positive is an oxygen in a
hydrogen negative is an oxygen and a
hydrogen
[Music]
okay we're going to touch
B can you see see
that negative yes yeah if we come out of
the water to our solid see that see how
it's not producing as much on the solid
difference even though we're really
close look right but then you go to the
mesh see the
mesh and then deeper you
go
see that'll just out of the as a
[Music]
negative you see that better mhm yeah
looks better yeah a lot better thank I'm
too close way no you don't want it to go
B oh don't worry
me what your
di we be soon and now lifted slightly
out pet as she comes past the where B
the
see the
difference slows down there yeah right
now W and mesh St still
scre now this one puts off more larger
oxygen bubbles see the larger oxygen
bubbles just put it down to the bottom
just in the middle same place as the
other can you see the larger oxygen
bubbles
now how can you tell the oxygen bubbles
cuz you can
burn but I
mean see hydrogen is the smallest right
it comes off the smallest and the oxygen
seems to be the
largest oxygen ones do not
um well you can see through them they're
not milky they're not uh small tiny
gassy or anything else right you see the
difference between this gas and the
other one then we got twice as much in
you see that mhm whatever we got twice
as much in up to here and it doesn't put
off nowhere near as much as that small
ring that's that one oh it's that one
understand mhm good now we got something
else to put in well what about a solid
okay let's try a solid you got don't
make it too long so we can see see it
all
right
see the larger bubbles move it to the
side move it to that
side
way so the closer you get she rips out
towards a
positive also positive comes in to
me coming off the outside more no that
one is roughed up a bit that one is
producing
right try not to get your thissing
because that's going to produce DP coer
yeah okay so your finer finer
bubbles right hardly any um larger
bubbles inside yeah no the larger
bubbles are not doing anything the
inside doesn't do anything you looking
the inside there nothing just the only
the only thing the inside is doing is
coming up from the right off the bottom
and then when you lowered it deep down
then your um your jum lead started
producing see and it's curled over and
went down in the top as he went deeper
nothing comes out of the middle it's
neutral
water you don't use
brass or copper anything goes green and
pollutes and will completely completely
oxidize up completely that one is only
been in for a couple of minutes yester
the afternoon and it is gone green now
we'll just show even with a
section all
right the size of the
bubbles all right as you move closer to
the mes how much more rapidly the gas is
produced from a threaded
section
okay see the gas coming away
[Music]
there the section here if we try and see
the uh see the unit on the uh around the
threaded section you'll see it start to
produce and then you'll notice that it's
a lot finer bubble or running off the
off the shiny of
face going have to get it to blow first
here you can see
that see how it's rapidly coming away
from the thread the threaded section
whereas it's not coming away as quickly
from Sur the shiny
[Music]
surface see this is different too
because when you've used
plates doesn't matter how thick The Chew
is doesn't matter how polished the sides
are or anything El she goes through the
current goes through M turns both sides
into positive and negative and produces
on both sides of those ples no matter
how thick they are we showed that other
do in with Peter's Che in it does not
have to be in
water there you
are this is just using another piece of
stainless um with
a um
yep
Ser than you got thanks
[Music]
I th a match in my
bucket you can't you can't make it go t
to get bubbles well if you get enough in
a close space you would I had a um I got
some balloons
yesterday it's coming out the
bottom of the gas uh where the rough
Edge is very little off
Surface the current is going straight
down the metal to the bottom and coming
out the rough Edge if you rough the
plate right up the edges you would see
it coming out the roughest she breaks
away this measures into wav and finer uh
stainless um completely sealed around
the um the threads of the of the mesh
actually and that doesn't produce a real
real lot it comes off the bottom as you
see if he pulls her out and then lowers
her in you'll see it coming from the
bottom because that's a rough Edge where
it's been cut